{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"225","name":"Renaissance Bowling Center","address":"19600 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48203","owner":"Virginia Douglas","licenseNumber":"033851","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.11766,42.43708","geojson":{"id":"225","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.117661356,42.437079945]},"properties":{"name":"Renaissance Bowling Center","owner":"Virginia Douglas","address":"19600 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48203","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"033851","establishmentid":"225","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"4/15/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"270","name":"Stonehouse Bar","address":"19803 Ralston","zipcode":"48203"},{"establishmentid":"51622929","name":"Asian Corned Beef","address":"19102 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48203"},{"establishmentid":"5032","name":"Tasty World","address":"19102 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"993","name":"Palmer Park Golf Course 3216","address":"19013 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48203"},{"establishmentid":"4836","name":"McDonald's","address":"1321 W Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"4822"},{"establishmentid":"4826","name":"Starbucks Coffee Co","address":"1327 W Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48203"},{"establishmentid":"51622792","name":"Lefty's","address":"1335 W Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48203"},{"establishmentid":"4704","name":"Subway","address":"1335 W Eight Mile ","zipcode":"48203"},{"establishmentid":"51622662","name":"Wingstop","address":"1331 W Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48203"},{"establishmentid":"4683","name":"Wing Stop","address":"1331 W Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48203"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"51175","inspectionDate":"2020-03-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Three compartment sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"On the Bar sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-03-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"violationCode":"4-204.11","violationDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood systems in FOOD preparation and WAREWASHING areas including components such as hoods, fans, guards, and ducting shall be designed to prevent grease or condensation from draining or dripping onto FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood system(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Designed to allow grease or condensation from draining/dripping onto","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Grease collection device","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \r\n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\r\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\r\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\r\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"dry","problemDescription":"Stored soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Towels","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"ENTIRE FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"49086","inspectionDate":"2019-09-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-09-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"On the floor Single service items","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-09-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In dishwash area","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Light bulb(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-09-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"45445","inspectionDate":"2019-03-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Stove","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"43166","inspectionDate":"2018-08-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-08-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"On the floor Single service items","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]},{"inspectionid":"41357","inspectionDate":"2018-01-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"Cleaning","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Thermometer(s)","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Utensil(s)","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Pitcher","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Beverage Dispenser","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Beverage Dispenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"On the floor Single service items","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]},{"inspectionid":"39571","inspectionDate":"2017-08-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at 30 inches above the floor","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Door frame","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"37933","inspectionDate":"2017-02-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink bar","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Near the Soap","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-02-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"On the floor Single service items","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Beverage Dispenser Holster(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"36125","inspectionDate":"2016-08-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"225"}}